Toggle navigation

[

](https://icai.org/)

    * * [Recent Opinions & Advisory Service Rules of Expert Advisory Committee](https://icai.org/category/recent-opinions-advisory-service-rules-of-expert-advisory-committee)

##### [Disciplinary Directorate](https://disc.icai.org/)  

##### [Career in ICAI](https://www.icai.org/post/career-in-icai)

##### [ICAI Call Sahayata](https://icai-call-sahayata.icai.org/)

##### [e-Journal](https://icai.org/category/e-journal)

##### [EOI/Tenders](https://www.icai.org/post/icai-eoi-tenders)

##### [ICAI Wall - Apps & Portals](https://icai.org/icaiwall.shtml)

##### [Institute's Program](https://www.icai.org/post/institute-program)

##### [New Scheme of Edu. & Training](https://www.icai.org/post/new-scheme-of-education-and-training)

##### [Placements](https://cmib.icai.org/)

##### [Notifications](https://icai.org/category/notifications)

Share this page:[](#)[](#)[](#)[](#)

1. ICAI Website - Privacy Policy

|     |
| --- |
| **ICAI Website Policy  <br>The Institute of Chartered Accountants of India** |
| **Privacy Policy** |
| ICAI website does not automatically capture any specific personal information from the user (like name, phone number or e-mail address) that allows us to identify users individually. If ICAI website requests you to provide personal information, you will be informed the particular purposes for which the information is gathered and adequate security measures will be taken to protect your personal information.  <br>  <br>We do not sell or share any personally identifiable information volunteered on the ICAI website to any third party (public/private). Any information provided to this website will be protected from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.  <br>  <br>We gather certain information about the user, such as Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, domain name, browser type, operating system, the date and time of the visit and the pages visited. We make no attempt to link these addresses with the identity of individuals visiting our site unless an attempt to damage the site has been detected. |

|     |
| --- |
|     |
|     |
|     |

Quick Links
===========

* [Site Map](javascript:void(0))

* |
* Copyright 2024 ICAI.
